[She's Wild Fire]
[Episode 4: Will You Trust Me?]
The 1991 Special Economic Zone
stock market
was a wealth-making machine.
[Stock Exchange]
Some people got rich overnight,
building fortunes out of thin air.
Others jumped in blindly,
and lost everything they had.
This is the wave of transformation
from a planned economy
to a market economy.
It's my only chance to turn things around.
My memories from my past life
are my biggest bargaining chip.
I didn't expect the 100,000-yuan business
you mentioned
to be stock trading.
It's not stock trading.
It's me
taking you along
to make a huge fortune.
Miss Xie really dares
to speak and dream big.
There is a saying:
"There are risks in the market.
Invest with caution."
For others, it's a risk,
but for me,
it's a business opportunity.
After the Southern Tour,
Shencheng will be the place to be.
And Shencheng Development Bank
is the local bank.
Its current stock price
is only the starting point.
As its business expands over time
and dividends are released,
there'll only be
more and more room to grow.
I didn't expect Miss Xie
to understand the stock market
so well.
Mr. Chu,
do you trust me?
I really do trust you.
I'm not in a hurry to get this money back.
No.
This is a matter of principle for me.
Alright then.
If we make a profit, I'll give you 20%.
If we lose, it's on me.
No.
I'll give you 20%.
Today in Shencheng,
there are plenty of people
who can come up with 100,000,
but I'm the only one
who can turn that 100,000
into a million.
If we lose,
I will bear all the losses.
[Chu Chunsheng's mother, Chu-Lin Jiahong]
Sell my shares
in Shencheng Development Bank.
If it drops again,
I'll be left with nothing.
Shencheng Development Bank is down again.
It's green again.
Whoever buys this lousy stock is cursed.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Hello.
Shencheng Development Bank.
1,200 shares.
1,200 shares?
That's 50,000 yuan.
Do you know anything about stocks?
Shencheng Development Bank
has been falling
for a month straight.
It's falling every day now.
You still dare to buy it?
God knows how many got trapped in this!
If you throw this 50,000 yuan in,
it will be gone in less than three days.
1,200 shares is too much money.
I think 500 shares is about right.
Is this woman crazy?
Look.
It dropped again.
What did I say?
This is a bottomless pit!
Miss.
Listen to an old lady's advice.
While you haven't lost too much,
sell it quickly.
Otherwise, when the market closes,
you won't even have a place to cry.
I'm buying more.
1,200 shares of Shencheng
Development Bank.
What?
Are you crazy?
You bought even more?
Have you not lost enough,
or do you want to ruin your family?
Breaking financial news.
To strongly support
financial growth
in the Shencheng Special Economic Zone,
the state has officially granted
1 billion RMB
in special support funds
to Shencheng Development Bank.
The funds will support the expansion
and upgrading of SEZ banks
to serve
the development of private enterprises.
At the same time,
Shencheng Development Bank
has formed strategic partnerships
with several Hong Kong conglomerates.
Huge good news!
Shencheng Development Bank
gets state support
to bring in Hong Kong capital
for expansion!
Favorable policies
and strong support!
It's going up.
Buy!
Buy Shencheng Development Bank for me,
no matter the price!
I'll buy too!
I want some too!
Buy Shencheng Development Bank for me,
no matter the price!
This 80,000 yuan
is just my stepping stone.
It won't be long
before I can leverage it into a million,
or even more.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for my business partner.
I want to buy you dinner.
Sure.
Then I won't stand on ceremony.
Since when did this place
start letting people
dressed like that in?
Look at how she's dressed.
So tacky.
Stop talking.
Man.
I heard your grandfather
wants to set you up with Chunsheng.
Have you two gone on a date yet?
Chunsheng is so busy.
How would he have time to date me?
Besides, you know what his mother is like.
Who could possibly meet her standards?
Chunsheng!
Chunsheng.
Why are you suddenly...
I've made plans with an important guest.
Let's talk another day.
What guest could be
more important than Man?
Chunsheng.
Sister Hong told me last week
you were away on business.
Why didn't you tell me you were back?
Yes.
I was away for two days.
I came back to discuss
an important business deal.
Business?
With her?
Yes.
Miss Xie is a very busy person
whom I finally managed to meet.
Whether I can have a meal with her
determines whether
we can continue working together.
If anyone interrupts us,
don't blame me
for disregarding our family ties
and having my manager escort you out.
After all, I wanted to have
my own restaurant
reserved exclusively for us.
But Miss Xie specifically reminded me
not to affect other guests' reservations.
That's why you were able
to come in and eat here today.
How could it be because of her?
What do you mean?
Let's go.
This lady must be
Miss Lin from Shencheng Hongji Industries.
Your father made his fortune
in the building materials business
and has consistently ranked
in the middle of Shencheng's rich list.
Good that you know.
Our family has a certain status
in Shencheng.
It's just a pity
that your father is now
jumping on the real estate bandwagon,
following the trend in real estate.
blindly expanding to acquire land.
Now that building material prices
are soaring,
your cash flow...
must be
getting a bit tight, isn't it?
What do you mean by that?
Let's go.
Why are you pulling me?
This lady
is wearing a Siluo dress.
It's still a relatively niche brand,
but in the next few years,
its price will definitely soar.
If you have a little money to spare,
I'd suggest investing
in this brand.
It would be more meaningful
than standing here
gossiping with your friends.
What are you trying to say,
you...
Miss Xie.
Everyone knows that
anyone who can dine here with Chunsheng
is no ordinary person.
After meeting you today,
I truly admire Chunsheng's eye.
If we have the chance in the future,
I hope we can work together.
Why are you giving her that?
Let's go.
Shen Man is very picky.
She never takes the initiative
to give someone her business card.
You're impressive.
What about you?
Have you ever taken the initiative
to give someone your card?
She and I are the same kind of people.
We never make
the first move to invite someone.
Because there are very few people
worth taking the initiative for.
Miss Xie,
may I have this dance?
My pleasure.
I've only known Miss Xie for a few days,
yet she always manages to surprise me.
She looks so young,
yet it seems like she's hiding
countless stories.
Yes.
I'm only 22 now.
What I can take control of again
isn't just my career,
but love as well.
Although you are very beautiful,
I would never
take advantage
of someone in a vulnerable position.
I only care about the patent.
Whoever can produce it
will get
my investment.
A person like you
doesn't deserve to be her father.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Then you can get to know me
a little more deeply.
Get to know you more deeply?
This time,
it's not about business.
Then show me a little more sincerity.
It's late. No loitering.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm looking at
my man.